Guide to the George Mason University Libraries records, 1949-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 4: Committees and collaborations, 1960-2004
  - Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC), Strategic Planning Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC), task force on library support for distance learners, undated (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC), task force on the cooperative center, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC), task force on the online catalog, 1985 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC), teaching research strategies, 1989 August (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC), warehouse, 1990-1992 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Washington Research Library Consortium (WRLC), Xlibris, 1993 June-July (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Women's studies Committee, 1989-1994 (Box 132, Folder 8)
- Series 5: Policies and procedures, 1960-2001
  Includes the library handbook, policies, emergency plans, computer and copier procedures and mission statements, for Fenwick library. Arranged alphabetically, then chronologically.
  - 5th floor elevator (emergency provisions), 1987 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Bomb threat procedures, 1971 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Borrowing privileges, 1977 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Building policies procedure, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Campus information (IT communications), 1993-1995 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Campus information training, 1994 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Campus information training, 1995 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Closed study carrels, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Computer labs compustat, undated (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Computer purchase guidelines, 1998 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Confidentiality (Library), 1989 march 21 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Copier costs, 1973-1975 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Librarians copyright act, 1982 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Copyright 1976 law and interpretations, 1982-1983 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Course reserve guidelines, forms, 1999 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Databases for GMU libraries, 1995 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Dealing with difficult people (instructions), 1993 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Departmental guide, 1980 (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - Draft policy, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - Educational leave for library faculty, undated (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - Elevators (Fenwick library), 1976 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - Emergency, disaster planning, 1984-1987 (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - Emergency prepardness plan, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 23)
  - Fenwick library emergency prepardness, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - Emergency, disaster plans, 2001 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Faculty handbook (library insert), 1974 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Fenwick library handbook and rules, 1974-1975 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - First search, 1994 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Fuel conservation, 1973-1974 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - General information (GMU libraries), 1984-1988 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - General reference allocations for branch libraries, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Gifts, 1973-1978 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    Acknowledgement guidelines and miscellaneous correspondence
  - GMU Foundation procedures, undated (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - GPO database, 1988-1994 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Guide to finding information at the GMU libraries, 1996-1997 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Guidelines for acquisition of electronic resources, 1990s (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Guidelines for consortium library projects, 1976 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Guidelines for service desk staff in answering questions, 1994 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - Handicapped policies, 1990 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - How to check out materials, Fenwick library, GMC, 1970 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Incident reporting system, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Inclement weather plan, 1989 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - Information for reception desk, 1973 (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - Information technology guide to services, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Internal control guidance manual, 1986 (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - Johnson center policies, 1996 (Box 134, Folder 22)
  - Library closing procedures, 1993 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Library compact - values, vision, and goals, 1998 (Box 134, Folder 23)
  - Library guide for students of education Alderman library (UVA), 1972 (Box 134, Folder 24)
  - Library handbook and faculty supplement, 1960 (Box 134, Folder 25)
  - Library handbook, 1961? (Box 134, Folder 26)
  - Library handbook, 1963-1964 (Box 134, Folder 27)
  - Library handbook, 1973? (Box 134, Folder 28)
  - Library handbook, 1977 (Box 134, Folder 29)
  - Library online catalog (user's guide) (ALIS), undated (Box 134, Folder 30)
  - Library of Congress information system (LOCIS), undated (Box 134, Folder 31)
  - LYNX tip sheet, undated (Box 134, Folder 32)
  - Mail delivery and pick-up, 1972-1975 (Box 134, Folder 33)
  - Draft style manual for the self-study in support of the reaffirmation of accreditation of GMU, 1999 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Mason link, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Media (acquisitions and video list), 1985 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Microforms guide, 1981-1983 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous internet information, 1995 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    Mason link, internet gopher, information client, electronic showcase outline
  - Miscellaneous organizational policies, 1991-2001 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous procedures (general), 1974-1975 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Mission statement, Fenwick library, 1989 February 15 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Mission statement, goals and objectives, 1981 March 18 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Monthly paychecks, 1972 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - North campus procedures manual, 1980 July (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Organizational charts, 1985-1992 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Staff organization chart, 1985 July (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Personal property, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - Library policies, 1981-1993 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Library policies, 1979-1984 (Box 135, Folder 16)
  - Library policies, 1983-1995 (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - Library policies, 1987-1988 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Library policies, 1994 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Library policies, 1994 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Library policies, 2000 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Policies and planning, 1989-1990 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Policy guidelines and procedures, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Library policy manual, 1979-1981 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Policy manual - Lorna, 1978-1980 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Privacy act, 1981-1983 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Procedures, printing, 1981-1982 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Library procedures, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Library procedures for summer session, 1971 summer (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Procedures for network troubleshooting, notification of evenings and weekends at Fenwick library, undated (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Procedures for updating reference collection, 1985 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Professional guidelines for librarians, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Public health nurse, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 16)
  - Publication guidelines (draft), undated (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - Publications, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Renewal policy and procedures, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 19)
  - Research guide, 1998-2000 (Box 136, Folder 20)
  - Reserve procedures, 1982 (Box 136, Folder 21)
  - Responsible use of computing, GMU UCIS folder, 1995 (Box 136, Folder 22)
  - Search strategy, 1987 July (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Student assistants manual, 1993 Fall (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Student assistants manual, microforms and government documents, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Student conduct policy, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Submitting and viewing contact reports, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Supplies, 1981 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Supplies and services, 1979-1982 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Surplus books, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Teaching resource strategy, 1986-1992 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Telephone manual, 1973 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Textbook adoption, 1990-1991 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Textbook criteria, 1990 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Travel, 1979-1982 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - University, 1976-1982 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - University policies, 1998 December 1 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - A User's Guide to Microforms in Fenwick Library, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Various safety measures, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Xlibris (information and how-to), 1993 (Box 137, Folder 17)
- Series 6: Buildings, 1962-2004
  Contains building plans, correspondence, and budgets on construction and renovation projects for Fenwick library, Johnson Center library (also referred to as the University Center), Arlington Campus Library, and the Mercer Library at the Prince William Campus. The series is divided into four subseries and is arranged alphabetically and then chronologically.
  - Subseries 6.1: Arlington Campus Library, 1978-1999
    Includes proposal for the Arlington Campus Library (also known as the Metro campus) as well as blueprints featuring the Arlington building and buildings at the Fairfax campus.
    - Arlington campus branch library, 1990, 1999 (Box 137, Folder 18)
      Academic programs, mission statement
    - Blueprint copies, 1982-1990 (Box 137, Folder 19)
      Fenwick, George's Hall, Metro Center, Robinson Hall, Thompson Hall
    - Carpeting and painting, 1999 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Metro campus, 1978-1982 (Box 137, Folder 20)
    - Metro campus, Law school library, 1979 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Phase 1, Arlington Campus task force, 1997-1999 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Phase 1, Arlington Campus task force, budget and space, 1997-1999 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Phase 1, Arlington Campus task force, information technology committee, 1998-2000 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Phase 1, space proposals, 1998-1999 (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Satellite campus proposal, 1977-1990 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Strategic plan, 2001-2004 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 6.2: Fenwick Library, 1962-2004
    Includes building plans, correspondence, proposals and specifications for the Fenwick Library building.
    - Academic building survey, 1967-1976 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Art and design collections, undated (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Articles about library design, 1990-1991 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Basement and building library, 1986-1988 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Equipment for new library, 1964 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Executive summary building program, 1987 June (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Facilities, Unversity maps, undated (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Facilities planning, Library addition budget request, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Fenwick library equipment list, undated (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Fenwick library floor plan, undated (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Fenwick library floor plan, 1980-1982 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Fenwick library lobby renovation, 2004 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Fenwick library site preparation, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Fifth floor, 1989-1991 (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - Fifth floor renovation, 1993 (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - Furnishings for Wing C, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - Furniture, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 19)
    - Higher education facilities act, 1964-1965 (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - Library addition, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 21)
    - Library building program, 1960-1963 (Box 138, Folder 22)
    - Library building program, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 23)
    - Library building program, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Library building program, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Library information, facility programs, building information, 1987-1989 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Library information, facility programs for Fenwick and the new library, 1989 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Library information, facility program for Fenwick library, 1987-1989 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Library program requirements, design and floor plans, 1966 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Library room numbers, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - North campus, 1980-1983 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Parking information (Fenwick), 1990-1995 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Physical facility, Library building phase I, 1965 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Physical facility program for Fenwick library, phase I, II, III, IV, 1988-1990 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Physical facility, Library building addition 1, phase II, 1969-1974 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Physical facility, phase II preliminary design, 1971 August 10 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Physical facility, Library III (desk), 1982-1984 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Physical facility, Library III, move (desk), 1983 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Physical facility, Library III, second floor, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Physical facility, phase IV, plans, 1987 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Physical facility, phase IV, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Physical facility, Library IV, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Physical facility, Library IV, preplanning study, 1981 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Physical facility, Phase IV, biennium, 1988-1990 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Physical facility, Phase IV, biennium, 1988-1990 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Physical facility, Library IV, 1989 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Preliminary program statement for a new library building, 1964 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Proposal for the student center, library IV facility, 1989 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Proposed library, 1968-1969 (Box 141, Folder 3)
      Blueprints, floor plans
    - Proposed library, preliminary plans, architect, 1964 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Signage for the library offices, 1980s (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Signage, Kroy Inc. GMU Kathy Perry, 1980s (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Signage, sent to faculty planning, 1985 January 29 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Signs, 1983 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Signs, 1978-1984 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Specifications, other libraries, 1962-1964 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Suggestions for planning the Northern Virginia Beach College in Fairfax, 1959 September 22 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Temperature and humidity, 1979-1980 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Tower I, 1970 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Tower II, 1979-1980 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Tower II, Building Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Tower II, libraries III, 1979-1980 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Tower III, 1988 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 6.3: Johnson Center (University Center) 1980-1996
    Includes budgets, building plans, correspondence, planning, proposals and policies relating to the Johnson Center building and library.
    - Art Chickering, Anne C. Moore's file, 1995 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Art Chickering, mission and programming, 1994-1995 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1993-1995 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1993-1997 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1993-1997 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1995 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Building plans, 1992-1993 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Building plans, background information University Center library, 1993-1994 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Building systems description, 1990-1991 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Celebration, Mason day flyer, 1993 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Collection development article, 1994 July (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Conference memo #3 with Marcellus Wright Cox and Smith Architects, 1991 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Core collection, Multicultural Collection Development Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Dedication fo the Johnson Center, 1996 April 11-12 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Design narrative preliminary submittal by Marcellus Wright Cox and Smith in association with Shepley Bulfinch Richardson and Abbott, 1990 November 1 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Drawings exterior and interior, undated (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Facility program for University Center library, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Facility program for University Center library, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Facility program with notes, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Fact sheet, named George W. Johnson Center, 1994-1995 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Fenwick and University Center relationship, 1995 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Floor plan, undated (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Furniture and equipment, 1980-1994 (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Furniture and equipment, development, shelving, proposal, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Furniture planning, 1992 (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - General correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - General correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Grand opening, 1996 April 11-12 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Grand opening, 1996 April 11-12 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      Steering committee
    - Holabird and Root architects, engineers, planners, portfolio, circa 1990 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Information, 1994 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Information, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      Diskette, floppy disk, slide
    - Initial planning, AT&T proposal, 1994 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      1 of 5
    - Initial planning, Library planning portion, 1992 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      2 of 5
    - Initial planning, architecture, 1990-1992 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      3 of 5
    - Initial planning, proposal and facility, 1990 November-December (Box 145, Folder 10)
      4 of 5
    - Initial planning, area summary and facility program, 1990 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      5 of 5
    - Inquiries, 1994 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Interior design, 1993 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Interior designers presentation interviews, 1993 April 21-22 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Johnson Center, 1993 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Johnson Center area summary, 1990-1991 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Johnson Center building plan, undated (Box 146, Folder 5)
      Floppy disk
    - Johnson Center facility program revision, 1990 November-December (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Johnson Center library facility program, 1991 November (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Johnson Center floor plan transparencies, undated (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Johnson Center information pamphlet, 1995-1996 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Johnson Center library miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Johnson Center planning, 1994-1995 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Justification, 1992-1993 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Kellogg Foundation proposal, 1996 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Library, 1989-1994 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Maintanence budget, 1990-1994 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Management and Operations Task Force, 1993-1994 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Management and Operations Task Force, 1994 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Management team, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - New Media Center proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Personnel, 1993-1995 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Planning information, 1980-1992 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Plans, 1994 August (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Policies, 1995 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Preplanning justification for GMU, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Presentation agenda by Deupi and associates Inc., 1993 April 22 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Deupi and Associates Inc., undated (Box 148, Folder 3)
      Handbook of projects and standard forms
    - Program plans, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 4)
      Includes two diskettes MD2D
    - Project proposal by Perry Dean Rogers and Partners, O'Dell Associates, 1989 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Proposal by Gensler and Associates architects, 1993 March 12 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Prooposal to provide interior design services for GMU submitted by AI, Boggs, 1993 March 12 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Proposal to provide design services by Studios Architecture, 1993 March 12 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Proposal for interior design services for the Commonwealth of Virginia GMU, 1993 March 12 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Publicity, 1993-1995 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Publicity, 1993-1996 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Revised facility program for University Center with questions (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Seminar on University Center planning, 1990 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Status report, 1994 March (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Subcommittee on technology, joint budget recommendation, 1994 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Task force, 1993 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Titles for University Center library by call number, undated (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 6.4: Prince William campus, 1991-1998
    - Prince William campus, 1991-1992 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Prince William campus, 1992 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Prince William Institute, 1992-1998 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Prince William Institute library, 1993 (Box 149, Folder 12)
- Series 7: Library departments and services, 1959-2008
  This series is divided into eight subseries each containing information on a particular department of the library. Arranged alphabetically, then chronologically.
  - Subseries 7.1: Catalog and databases, 1979-1995
    Contains information on the automated library system, and cataloging department.
    - Automated library system (ALIS), 1986 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Automated library system (ALIS) replacement, 1987 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - Book plates, undated (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Cataloging, processing departmental procedures and policies, 1980 (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - CD-Rom databases, 1988-1995 (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Database information notebook, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Main card catalog, 1986 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Cataloging, management by objective, 1979 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - NEXIS database search, 1984, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Online catalog, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - OPAC, 1992 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Proquest, 1995 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - University of California MELVYL computer link system, 1989 March (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 7.2: Circulation, 1959-2002
    Includes manuals and policies for the circulation department.
    - Circulation, 1967 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Circulation, 1984-1996 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Circulation, 1990s (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Circulation, policy changes, 2001-2002 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Circulation manual, 1980 September (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Circulation manual, Circa 1980 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Circulation policies for SMT management, 1998 December 10 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Circulation shelving, 1987-1989 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Circulation, student assistant handbook, 1984 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Circulation, student assistant handbook, 1984 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Data phase, 1982-1985 (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Data phase, 1982-1985 (Box 150, Folder 20)
    - Data phase, 1982-1985 (Box 150, Folder 21)
    - Data phase user meeting, Kansas City, 1985 (Box 150, Folder 22)
    - Data phase, OCLC, 1986 February (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Data phase, OCLC conversion, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Historical interlibrary loan (ILL), 1959-1979 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Interlibrary loan (ILL), 1983-1988 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Interlibrary loan (ILL), 1985-1989 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Library (main campus) library borrowers card, undated (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Management by objective, circulation, 1979 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 7.3: Collection development, 1964-2001
    Contains acquisitions information, collection development policies, and lists of audiovisual materials in the library.
    - Acquisitions, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Collection development, 1991-1992 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Collection development, acquisitions, Wang institute library, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Collection development policy statement, 1983-1985 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Collection development policy statement, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Collection development policy statement, 1992 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Collection development policy statement, 1995 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Collection development policy revision, 2001 March (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Collection development report, 1981 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Collection development selectors meetings, 1994 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Collection management, 1981-1989 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Collection management, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 3)